PREVIOUSLY ON
PRETTY LITTLE LIARS.
WHAT HAPPENED IN THE WOODS?
TOBY CAVANAUGH IS DEAD.
SOMEBODY KILLED HIM.
I SAW HIS BODY.
AHH!
OH, GOD.
MAGGIE, I AM SO SORRY.
DID PASTOR TED
HIRE SOMEBODY TO WORK
ON THE CHURCH?
Hannah: I PUT A FIVE DOLLAR BILL
IN THE CHURCH COLLECTION BOX,
IT HAD SOME DICE DRAWN ON IT.
AND LATER THAT DAY,
CALEB'S DAD HAD IT.
DO YOU REALLY THINK HE
WOULD STEAL FROM THE PLACE
THAT JUST HIRED HIM?
THERE WAS SOME TROUBLE
WITH THE OLD BADGES.
PEOPLE GETTING IN?
PEOPLE GETTING OUT?
EZRA FITZ HAS APPLIED
AS A SUBSTITUTE TEACHER.
I HAVE TO ASK,
ARE YOU SEEING EZRA FITS?
NO, I'M NOT.
ALL I WANT FROM YOU
AND YOUR MOTHER IS THAT CAR.
LOOK AT ALL THAT'S HAPPENED
SINCE YOU TURNED ME DOWN
ON OUR LITTLE DRIVE
UP THE MOUNTAIN.
BUT I BELIEVE IN SECOND CHANCES.
YOU NEED ME.
( door buzzing )
YOU HAVE VISITORS.
SPENCER?
I'LL BE IN THE HALL
IF YOU NEED ME.
Emily: HEY. YOU KNEW
WE WERE COMING, RIGHT?
WE SPOKE WITH YOUR MOM.
WE WANTED TO BE HERE
THE FIRST DAY.
BUT SHE SAID YOU WERE GOING
TO BE HOME TOMORROW, SO...
SHE STILL BELIEVES THAT?
SHE THINKS THAT I'LL BE ABLE
TO SLEEP THROUGH THE NIGHT
IF I JUST TAKE A NICE BUBBLE
BATH AND LAY IN MY OWN BED?
I THINK WHAT SHE WANTS IS--
I KNOW WHAT SHE WANTS, BUT
THEY DON'T MAKE A LOOFA
THAT SCRAPES OUT
THE INSIDE OF YOUR HEAD.
THE PARK RANGERS FOUND A BODY.
Emily and Aria: HANNAH!
WHAT?
THE SOONER SHE KNOWS,
THE SOONER SHE CHECKS
OUT OF THIS PLACE.
WHAT HANNAH IS TRYING TO SAY
IS WE HAVE GOOD NEWS.
THEY FOUND A BODY
IN THE WOODS.
THE POLICE BELIEVE
IT WAS A CAMPER.
IT WAS TOBY.
NO, SPENCE, IT WASN'T.
THIS PERSON, HE'D BEEN
MISSING FOR AWHILE
AND HE WAS NOWHERE NEAR WHERE
YOU THOUGHT YOU SAW--
I KNOW WHAT I SAW.
IT WAS TOBY.
HEY, SO, UM,
I WAS THINKING
TOMORROW NIGHT
WHEN YOU GET HOME,
WE COULD ALL--
I NEED TO STAY HERE.
I NEED MORE TIME.
TIME FOR WHAT?
HANNAH.
SHUFFLING AROUND IN
MONA'S OLD SLIPPERS
ISN'T GOING TO GET
HER ANY BETTER.
HANNAH, CHILL.
YOU KNOW WHAT...
I WOULD NOT DINE HERE,
IF I WERE YOU,
I HAD TO SNEAK AROUND
IN THAT KITCHEN,
AND I SAW A ROACH
BIG ENOUGH TO WEAR AN APRON.
MOVING. ON.
YOU ARE NOT CRAZY.
THIS PLACE IS.
I'M TOO TIRED TO HAVE
THIS FIGHT RIGHT NOW, GUYS.
I FEEL SAFE HERE.
THOSE BARS DON'T JUST KEEP
YOU FROM GETTING OUT,
THEY KEEP OTHER PEOPLE
FROM GETTING IN.
( knocking on door )
UH, NEED A MINUTE.
YOUR FRIENDS ARE LEAVING.
DO YOU WANT TO SAY GOOD-BYE?
I ALREADY DID.
♪ GOT A SECRET,
CAN YOU KEEP ♪
♪ IT'S WHERE THIS ONE
YOU SAVE ♪
♪ GOT A LOCKET,
IN YOUR POCKET ♪
♪ TAKING THIS ONE
TO THE GRAVE ♪
♪ EVER SHOW YOU
THAT I KNOW YOU ♪
♪ WON'T TELL WHAT I SAID
♪ 'CAUSE TWO CAN
KEEP A SECRET ♪
♪ IF ONE OF THEM IS DEAD
Hannah: HAVE YOU SEEN
MY MAKE-UP BAG?
( sighs )
NO, BUT I THINK
EVERYTHING
THAT WAS IN IT
IS ON MY PILLOW.
OKAY, DON'T START.
I ONLY SLEPT FOR,
LIKE, 20 MINUTES.
Emily: WHY DO YOU
KEEP LOOKING OUT THERE?
BECAUSE WILDEN KNOWS
I'M STAYING HERE.
THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE
THINKING ABOUT?
I'M HAVING DREAMS ABOUT OUR
FRIEND HAVING HER HEAD SHAVED,
AND YOU'RE LOOKING--
I HAVE LOTS OF OTHER THINGS
THAT ARE KEEPING ME
UP AT NIGHT,
OKAY EMILY?
IF THAT CAR I DUNKED SUDDENLY
LEARNS HOW TO FLOAT, THEN--
IF WILDEN'S LOOKING
FOR HIS CAR,
THEN HE'S NOT A.
OKAY, BESIDES CARS
DON'T FLOAT, IF THEY DID,
PILGRIMS COULD
HAVE DRIVEN HERE.
WHY IS THERE
A WET TOWEL ON MY BED?
( knock on door )
Pam: LADIES,
YOU BETTER GET HOPPING,
OR YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO HAVE TIME FOR BREAKFAST.
Hannah:
OH, NONE FOR ME, THANKS.
YOU KNOW I LOVE HER,
BUT SOMEBODY'S GOT TO TEACH
THAT GIRL THE WORD "FOLD."
IT WAS A ROUGH NIGHT.
HONEY, LOOK. I KNOW IT'S HARD
SEEING A FRIEND SUFFER,
BUT IF THE DOCTOR'S
THINK SHE--
DOCTORS AREN'T
HELPING SPENCER.
OKAY, SHE STILL
BELIEVES THAT WAS TOBY.
WELL, YOU CAN'T GET CAUGHT
UP IN THAT KIND OF THINKING.
DON'T TAKE ON A TRAGEDY THAT
HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH YOU.
MOM! OKAY, YOU WORK
AT THE PRECINCT,
CAN YOU AT LEAST TELL ME WHEN
YOU KNOW MORE ABOUT THE BODY?
( sighs )
LOOK,
IF IT'LL HELP YOU
MOVE ON FROM THIS,
THEN YES.
YOU'LL KNOW WHEN I KNOW.
SURE IF THIS IS
BIG ENOUGH TO SPLIT?
I THINK THAT WE SHOULD
GO SIT INSIDE.
WE COULD ALSO EAT
THIS IN MY CAR
AND DUCK EVERY TIME
SOMEBODY WALKS BY.
IF I'M TELLING THE PRINCIPAL
THAT WE'RE NOT INVOLVED,
I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD
BE SEEN SPLITTING
A CRULLER ON
THE SIDEWALK.
ALL RIGHT,
WE'RE NOT
GOING BACKWARDS.
WE'LL FIGURE IT OUT.
LOOK...
NOTHING BETWEEN US
NEEDS TO CHANGE.
( phone ringing )
IT'S MAGGIE.
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
WHAT TIME?
TOMORROW...
UM, NO, I JUST HAVE A...
YOU KNOW WHAT, YEAH.
I CAN PICK HIM UP.
YEP.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
MALCOLM'S KARATE CLASS
GETS OUT AT THE SAME TIME
AS MY SECOND INTERVIEW.
WELL, I'D OFFER TO HELP,
I JUST FIGURED
AFTER THE WHOLE
FALLING-OFF-THE-BED
INCIDENT--
WELL, YOU KNOW
I DON'T BLAME YOU
FOR THAT.
IT'S NOT ABOUT ME.
SO, MAGGIE BLAMES ME.
YOU KNOW WHAT,
HONESTLY,
I WOULD LOVE IT IF
YOU PICKED UP MALCOLM.
IF I PUT OFF
THIS INTERVIEW,
SOMEONE ELSE IS
GOING TO GET THAT JOB.
( laughs )
WELL, WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO TELL MAGGIE?
I CAN DEAL WITH HER.
AND WHAT'S EVEN TRIPPIER
IS WE BOTH HAVE SCARS
BELOW OUR LEFT KNEE.
AND, YOU KNOW, GRANTED,
MY DAD GOT HIS
IN PRISON, BUT...
THAT WAS A JOKE.
( laughs )
MMM, WHAT'S THAT SMELL?
NEW PERFUME?
NO, IT'S AIR FRESHENER.
EMILY'S MOM SPRAYED IT
ALL OVER MY CLOTHES AND THEN,
WHEN I WASN'T LOOKING,
SHE SPRAYED IT IN MY HAIR.
ASK HER TO SPRITZ
YOU TONIGHT.
MY DAD WANTS TO TAKE US
TO A NICE DINNER.
CALEB, HE DOES NOT
HAVE TO DO THAT.
STOP.
LOOK, NOT ONLY ARE
YOU THE PERSON THAT
BROUGHT HIM BACK
INTO MY LIFE,
BUT YOU'RE THE REASON
HE GETS TO STAY IN IT.
AND YOU GOT THE MAN WORK.
LET HIM GET YOU AN ENTRé.
CAN'T YOU JUST ASK YOUR MOM FOR
A COPY OF THE CORONER'S REPORT?
ARIA, THE REPORT
DOESN'T SAY NOT TOBY,
IT SAYS JOHN DOE.
IT'S NOT GOING TO
CHANGE SPENCER'S MIND.
( phone rings )
WHO'S THAT?
UM, SHANA.
WHY DOES SHE KEEP TEXTING YOU
WHILE PAIGE IS OUT OF TOWN?
IS SHE INTO YOU?
SORRY YOU GUYS,
CALEB HAD A LOT TO SHARE.
WHY ARE YOU BLUSHING?
WHY IS SHE BLUSHING?
SHANA'S CRUISING HER,
AND I THINK THAT SHE
SHOULD SHUT IT DOWN
BEFORE IT TURNS INTO
EX AND THE CITY.
GUYS, I'M NOT
THINKING ABOUT SHANA.
WE NEED TO HELP SPENCER.
NO, EM,
YOU SAW HER FACE.
SHE'S NOT GETTING
OUT OF THERE
UNLESS WE KIDNAP HER.
OR WE ACTUALLY TAKE
THE BODY THERE AND PROVE
TO HER IT ISN'T TOBY.
EM, THAT'S NOT
A REAL OPTION.
NO, BUT, TAKING
A PICTURE OF IT IS.
AND WE'VE BEEN TO
THAT MORGUE BEFORE,
WHAT'S STOPPING US
FROM GOING BACK?
UM, DO WE REALLY
HAVE TO ANSWER THAT?
Eddie:
EVER PLAYED THIS ONE?
UM, NO. LOOKS LIKE IT'S
A BIT BEFORE MY TIME.
SO IS DUKE ELLINGTON.
IF HE WALKS IN THE DOOR,
ARE YOU GOING TO ASK HIM
NOT TO PLAY THE PIANO?
Wren: SPENCER? I JUST
LEARNED YOU'RE ADMITTED.
I DIDN'T KNOW.
EDDIE, UH, COULD YOU
CHECK ON MR. PATERSON?
HE MAY NEED ASSISTANCE
GETTING TO PHYSICAL THERAPY.
HE HAD IT THIS MORNING.
THEN, PERHAPS YOU
COULD DO A FOLLOW-UP,
CHECK ON
HIS PAIN MANAGEMENT.
HOW'RE YOU FEELING?
UM...
SPENCER, IF THERE'S
ANYTHING I SAID OR DID THAT--
NO, YOU'RE NOT
THE REASON THAT I'M HERE.
WHO CHOSE THIS GAME?
YOU OR EDDIE?
EDDIE. WHY?
HE PLAYED IT WITH MONA,
WHEN SHE FIRST ARRIVED.
YEAH, SHE WAS
A BIT OBSESSED WITH IT,
UNTIL SHE EVENTUALLY
TRADED IT FOR CARDS.
( phone ringing )
I'M AFRAID I'VE GOT
TO PUSH ON.
I'LL CHECK ON YOU LATER.
OKAY.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
HANNAH?
I'VE LEFT YOUR MOM
SEVERAL MESSAGES
AND I HAVEN'T HEARD BACK.
IS THERE A BETTER WAY
THAT I CAN REACH HER?
UH, SHE'S IN NEW YORK RIGHT
NOW FOR A TRAINING SEMINAR.
WHY, WHAT'S WRONG?
WE JUST NEED HER TO WEIGH
IN ON A DELICATE ISSUE.
WHO'S WE?
MRS. MONTGOMERY,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
( sighs )
I'M ON THE CHURCH'S
RESTORATION COMMITTEE,
AND SOMETHING'S COME UP.
WAIT, IS THIS
ABOUT CALEB'S DAD?
( sighs )
HOW WELL DID YOUR MOM
KNOW JAMIE BEFORE
SHE RECOMMENDED HIM?
LOOK, I'M TRYING TO HELP.
IT'S JUST, IT'S REALLY
HARD TO DEFEND THE HONOR
OF SOMEONE
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW.
I'M HOPING IT'S ALL JUST
A BIG MISUNDERSTANDING.
AND WHAT'S
THE MISUNDERSTANDING?
JAMIE...REMOVED
THE BRONZE BELL
FROM THE TOWER
TO HAVE IT REPAIRED,
BUT THE ONE THAT WAS
RETURNED IS EVIDENTLY
OF MUCH LESSER VALUE.
WAIT, THAT'S WHAT
THIS IS ABOUT?
THEY MISS THEIR OLD,
CRUSTY BELL?
TO THE TUNE OF $8,000.
PLEASE, DON'T SAY
ANYTHING TO CALEB,
JUST HAVE YOUR
MOM CALL ME.
IT'S GOT GREAT BONES.
THEY BUILT THESE CHURCHES
TO LAST.
WHEN DO THEY EXPECT
YOU TO BE DONE?
I'M GOING TO TAKE MY TIME.
I WANT TO GET THIS RIGHT.
OH, BEFORE I FORGET.
WHAT IS THIS?
IT'S FOR YOU.
OPEN IT.
IT'S AN ANGEL.
IT SEEMED APPROPRIATE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
( phone ringing )
OH, I HATE
THESE DAMN THINGS.
LET ME TURN THIS OFF.
ACTUALLY, IT'S PASTOR TED.
I MAY HAVE TO GET THIS,
EXCUSE ME.
HELLO?
Veronica: I THOUGHT THIS MIGHT
MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER.
AND THEN MAYBE ON
THE WAY HOME, WE CAN STOP--
I'M NOT COMING HOME.
JUST AT LEAST PUT
ON THE BLOUSE.
MOM, I TOLD YOU
I'M NOT READY.
WELL, AS SOON AS YOU'RE
IN YOUR OWN BEDROOM,
SURROUNDED BY YOUR--
LOOK, MOM,
I CAN'T JUST GO BACK
TO DINNERS AT THE CLUB.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WEAR
THE BLAZER, JUST PUT ON THE--
( yelling)
I SAID I'M NOT READY!
WHAT HAPPENED BETWEEN
YOU AND TOBY?
I'M NOT MOVING FROM THIS SPOT
UNTIL I GET A REAL ANSWER.
THE LAST TIME I SAW
SOMEONE IN THIS STATE,
CLINGING TO A SECRET
THIS HARD, IT WAS ALISON.
A FEW WEEKS LATER
SHE WAS DEAD.
( door opens )
( sighs )
ALISON.
WHERE WERE YOU?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
ASLEEP IN SPENCER'S ROOM.
I HAD TO GO OUT.
FOR WHAT?
WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR MOUTH?
IT'S BLEEDING.
I MUST'VE SCRATCHED
MYSELF ON A TREE BRANCH
ON MY WAY OVER
TO THE HOUSE.
CAN I GO UPSTAIRS,
PLEASE?
WHY DID YOU HAVE TO GO TO YOUR
HOUSE AT THREE IN THE MORNING?
MRS. HASTINGS, PLEASE.
I CAN'T TALK ABOUT THIS.
LET ME GET SOME ICE
FOR YOUR MOUTH.
JUST STAY THERE.
PLEASE?
HERE.
DID YOU HAVE A FIGHT
WITH SOMEONE?
MRS. HASTINGS, IF YOU
TELL MY PARENTS,
IT'S ONLY GOING
TO MAKE IT WORSE.
PROMISE ME YOU WON'T
SAY ANYTHING.
COME HERE.
SHH.
I'M JUST BEING WEIRD.
OVERLY SENSITIVE.
I'M FINE.
YOU NEVER TOLD THIS
TO THE POLICE?
OF COURSE I DID.
BUT I MADE UP MY OWN MIND ABOUT
WHO WENT AFTER HER THAT NIGHT
AND I KEPT THAT TO MYSELF.
WELL, WHO?
WHY? MOM, HOW COULD
YOU NOT SAY ANYTHING?
BECAUSE IF JASON
WENT AFTER US,
EXPOSING YOUR FATHER
AS HIS, TOO,
IT'D BE MY FAMILY BREAKING DOWN
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.
SO, YOU STILL
BELIEVE JASON?
NO, I DON'T.
NOT ANYMORE.
BUT I'M STARTING
TO WONDER ABOUT OTHERS.
I NEED TO ASK.
IS TOBY NOT THE PERSON
THAT WE THOUGHT HE WAS?
SORRY, GUYS, I'M GOING
TO HAVE TO HIT THE ROAD.
THERE'S A PROBLEM AT WORK
I GOTTA DEAL WITH.
WHAT, RIGHT NOW?
I'VE JUST BEEN FIRED.
WHAT--WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
IT SEEMS THE WRONG BELL
GOT HUNG UP IN THE TOWER...
I'M GONNA HAVE TO GO DOWN
TO THE FOUNDRY MYSELF
AND CLEAR THIS UP.
DO YOU WANT ME
TO COME WITH YOU?
NO, YOU GUYS
FINISH YOUR DINNER,
I'LL SORT THIS OUT.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
( door closing )
OKAY, WHO AM I SUPPOSED
TO TEXT IF I SEE SOMEONE?
ME. NOT HANNAH.
WE'RE USING HER PHONE
TO TAKE THE PICTURE.
HANNAH, PAY ATTENTION.
WHAT? I'M SORRY.
MY BOYFRIEND'S DAD
GOT NAILED FOR STEALING.
WHERE DO YOU SELL
A HOT BELL, ANYWAY?
HANNAH, FOCUS.
I DON'T WANT TO BE
IN THERE ANY LONGER
THAN WE HAVE TO.
WE FIND JOHN DOE,
WE TAKE THE PICTURE,
AND WE GET OUT OF HERE.
IF IT'S BRONZE,
YOU PROBABLY MELT
IT DOWN FIRST.
MELT IT INTO WHAT?
WHY ARE WE STILL
DISCUSSING BELLS?
BECAUSE CALEB THINKS
HIS DAD IS A SAINT,
AND I KNOW HE'S SELLING PIECES
OF OUR CHURCH ONLINE.
OKAY, FORGET IT.
I'LL DO THIS ALONE.
Hannah: HOW ARE WE GONNA KNOW
WHICH ONE IS JOHN DOE?
Emily: WE HAVE TO GO
THROUGH THOSE RACKS.
UM, NO.
YOU ARE GOING
THROUGH THOSE RACKS.
THIS ISN'T A CLEARANCE SALE,
EMILY, AND I'M FREAKING OUT.
ALL WE'VE DONE IS WALK
THROUGH THOSE DOORS.
IT DOESN'T MATTER!
I SMELL DEAD PEOPLE.
FINE, JUST GET
YOUR PHONE READY, OKAY?
I'LL HOLD IT,
BUT YOU HAVE TO AIM IT.
I JUST WANT TO
CLOSE MY EYES.
Hannah:
GOD, THIS IS SO WRONG.
YOU SPEND YOUR WHOLE LIFE
DOING CRUNCHES,
GETTING RID OF TAN LINES,
NOT EATING THAT SECOND PUDDING.
AND THEN IN THE END YOU'RE
JUST A STALE LOAF OF BREAD
LYING ON A RACK.
UM, MAYBE YOU CAN HELP ME
WITH THIS LOAF,
I CAN'T FIND
THE TAG.
WAIT.
EM, WHAT IF IT REALLY
IS TOBY IN THERE?
IT'S NOT. AND SPENCER
NEEDS TO KNOW THAT.
'KAY, BUT JUST IN CASE,
I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN
HANDLE SEEING HIS FACE.
SO CAN WE JUST LOOK FOR
HIS TATTOO,
OR SOMETHING?
IT'S NOT TOBY!
( cell phone beeps )
( door closes )
( elevator bell dings )
Emily:
AHH!
( cell phone rings )
EM, SOMEONE'S COMING.
COME ON, WE HAVE TO GO.
EM, COME ON!
( knocking on door )
HI, SUNSHINE.
HEY.
GOOD BOOK?
IT'S OKAY.
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
THAT GAME THAT YOU WANTED
TO PLAY YESTERDAY?
I HEARD IT WAS ONE OF
MONA'S FAVORITES.
WHO PLAYED IT WITH HER?
I DON'T RECALL.
MONA LIKED TO PLAY
A LOT OF GAMES.
YEAH, BUT WREN...
DR. KINGSTON,
HE SAID SHE WAS
"OBSESSED" WITH
THIS ONE.
WELL, HE WOULD KNOW.
WHAT IS WITH YOU AND HIM?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
EDDIE, ARE YOU THE PERSON
BEHIND THE TROUBLE
WITH THE VISITORS' PASSES?
DID YOU LET
SOMEBODY IN WHO--
IT WASN'T ME.
WAS IT DR. KINGSTON?
TAKE YOUR PILL.
YOU MAY BE SLEEPING,
BUT YOU DON'T LOOK
LIKE YOU'RE
GETTING ANY REST.
I WON'T TELL ANYBODY.
TRUST YOUR INSTINCT.
MINE TOLD ME,
FROM THE MINUTE
THAT GUY GOT HERE,
IT WASN'T FOR
THE RIGHT REASONS.
LET'S JUST
LEAVE IT AT THAT, OKAY?
HEY.
DID YOU GET MY MESSAGES?
YEAH, I'VE BEEN
CRAMMING FOR ALGEBRA.
I HAVE A MAKE-UP TEST IN,
LIKE, TEN MINUTES.
WELL, MY DAD'S SCREWED.
THE FOUNDRY CLAIMS
THERE IS NO MIX-UP,
AND THEY HAVE
THE PAPER TRAIL TO PROVE IT.
WELL, MAYBE IF
YOUR FATHER SPOKE TO
THE CHURCH COMMITTEE,
AND TOLD THEM THAT--
TOLD THEM WHAT?
WHY SHOULD HE HAVE TO DEFEND
HIMSELF TO A BUNCH OF
SMALL-MINDED PEOPLE WHO
THINK SOMEONE IS A THIEF
JUST BECAUSE THEY
DON'T TUCK IN THEIR SHIRT?
DID I PRESS
MUTE OR SOMETHING?
WHY ARE YOU BEING SO QUIET?
I'M JUST LISTENING.
YOU DID A LOT OF
THAT LAST NIGHT, TOO.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY, CALEB.
SINCE WHEN?
HANNAH YOU HAVE
AN OPINION ABOUT
EVERYTHING,
FROM HONEY BOO-BOO'S
HAIR CUT
TO THE WEIRD LOOK
THE LUNCH LADY
GAVE YOU WHEN
YOU ASKED FOR
BUTTER ON YOUR CORN.
LOOK, I JUST
DON'T THINK THAT
YOUR DAD HAS
CHANGED AS MUCH
AS MUCH AS YOU
THINK HE HAS.
LOOK, THE NIGHT
THAT HE GOT THE JOB
AT THE CHURCH,
I PUT MONEY IN
THE CHURCH COLLECTION BOX,
AND WHEN HE PAID
FOR THE PIZZA,
HE USED THAT SAME BILL.
HOW COULD YOU
POSSIBLY KNOW THAT?
BECAUSE THERE WAS A PAIR
OF LUCKY DICE DRAWN ON IT.
IT WAS THE SAME BILL,
CALEB.
( school bell rings )
( scattered chattering )
HI. EXCUSE ME, YEAH,
I'M HERE TO PICK UP MALCOLM.
OH, HE WAS ALREADY PICKED UP
ABOUT TEN MINUTES AGO.
HE WAS?
OH, SO MAGGIE MUST HAVE--
OH, NO, HIS MOM DIDN'T COME
TODAY, IT WAS A FRIEND.
UH, ARIA MONTGOMERY.
SOMETHING WRONG?
NO. NO,
EVERYTHING'S FINE, THANKS.
( carnival music playing )
( children laughing )
( laughing )
Carnival barker:
KNOCK THEM DOWN AND WIN A PRIZE!
( carnival barker continues )
( laughter )
Ella:
ARIA?
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE
COMING HERE TONIGHT.
YEAH, I'M CAME TO MEET UP
WITH EZRA AND MALCOLM.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
IS MAGGIE HERE, TOO?
I DON'T KNOW, MAYBE.
HONEY, WE TALKED
ABOUT THIS.
AND I KNOW YOU WANT
TO MAKE IT WORK, BUT--
OKAY, MOM, I CAN'T
DO THIS RIGHT NOW.
ARIA!
YOU'RE GOING TO BE
THE ONE THAT GETS HURT.
NOT TO MENTION
A CONFUSED LITTLE BOY
WHO'S STILL WONDERING
HOW THIS STRANGER
IS SUDDENLY HIS FATHER.
HE NEEDS HELP
WORKING THROUGH IT,
BUT NOT WITH YOU.
MALCOLM ALREADY
HAS SOMEBODY LOOKING
OUT FOR HIM.
I HAVE TO GO.
BE RIGHT BACK, I'M GOING
TO DROP THIS OFF TO ROOM 217.
WHAT IS THAT?
A BOOK.
ONE OF THE PATIENTS WAS
ASKING FOR IT EARLIER, SO--
YES, WELL, OUR PATIENT
NEEDS HER REST.
YOU CAN GIVE IT
TO SPENCER TOMORROW.
I'M OFF TOMORROW.
ALL RIGHT, THEN I'LL
GIVE IT TO HER FOR YOU.
WE'RE NOT HAVING THE SAME
PROBLEM AGAIN, ARE WE, EDDIE?
( fair music playing )
HAVE YOU HEARD
ANYTHING YET?
NOPE.
( phone rings )
FOR ALL I KNOW,
HE'S ALREADY SKIPPED TOWN.
WELL, I SPOKE TO MY MOM--
HANNAH, IT'S NOT UP
TO YOUR MOM
OR YOU, OR ME TO
DIG HIM OUT OF THIS.
IS THIS EVERYTHING?
YEAH, ALMOST.
JUST TO FIND MY ENGLISH BOOK.
ALL RIGHT,
I'LL BE OUT FRONT.
( door bell rings )
Jamie: HEY.
I WAS ON MY WAY TO YOUR PLACE,
AND I SAW YOUR CAR OUT FRONT.
WHERE WERE YOU?
OH, MAKING PHONE CALLS...
HEY.
WAS TRYING TO TRACK DOWN
A GUY WHO HELPED ME
WITH THE DRY WALL.
AND SEE IF HE CAN HELP...
HELP WITH WHAT?
BACK UP YOUR STORY?
WHAT'S HIS CUT?
WHAT?
CALEB,
DON'T DO THIS RIGHT NOW.
HEY, YOU SHOULD LISTEN
TO YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
I AM.
AND I BELIEVE HER
WHEN SHE SAYS THIS
ISN'T THE FIRST TIME
THAT YOU'VE STOLEN
FROM THAT CHURCH.
WHAT ARE WE
TALKING ABOUT HERE?
WE AREN'T TALKING.
WE ARE DONE.
LAST NIGHT,
YOU WERE MY DEFENDER.
WHAT HAPPENED?
I WOKE UP,
AND I REALIZED THAT
THIS ISN'T THE FIRST TIME
THAT YOU'VE SCREWED ME OVER.
OH, I SEE.
I'M STILL THAT PERSON,
HUH?
SOMEHOW YOU MANAGED
TO FORGIVE YOUR MOTHER'S SINS.
DON'T SUPPOSE IT'S GOT ANYTHING
TO DO WITH THAT FANCY CAR
SHE TOSSED AT YOU.
THAT HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH THIS.
MAYBE NOT, BUT IT'S GOT TO
BE EASIER TO POINT A FINGER
AT SOMEONE WITH A RUSTY PICK-UP
AND NO PERMANENT ADDRESS.
ISN'T THAT ALL
THE PROOF YOU NEEDED?
ALL THE PROOF THAT I NEEDED
WERE THE RATTY HAND-ME-DOWNS
THAT I HAD AS A KID.
REMEMBER THE WINTER COAT
THAT ENDED AT MY ELBOW?
AND THE UNSIGNED
PERMISSION SLIPS?
AND THE SOCIAL WORKERS,
AND THE FOSTER FAMILIES
WHO SLAMMED DOORS IN
MY FACE WHEN THEY WERE
TIRED OF LOOKING AT ME?
THAT IS MY PROOF!
YEAH.
WOW, WHEN YOU
PUT IT THAT WAY...
I GUESS I WOULDN'T
BELIEVE ME, EITHER.
Aria:
SHOULD I CALL THE POLICE?
Emily:
YES. WAIT.
UNLESS YOU THINK
IT WILL MAKE IT WORSE.
WHAT'S WORSE?
A'S GOT EZRA'S KID.
I'M JUST SAYING, YOU SAW THEM,
MALCOLM WASN'T HURT.
BUT IF YOU CALL THE COPS,
A MIGHT--
DON'T. JUST DON'T.
OKAY, I SWEAR, IF SOMETHING
HAPPENS TO THAT LITTLE BOY
BECAUSE OF ME, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'M GOING TO DO.
ARIA. WALK OVER TO
THE POLICE STATION,
AND REPORT IT.
I'LL MEET YOU THERE IN TEN.
( sighs )
MALCOLM?
THERE'S GONNA BE ANOTHER SHOW.
THE MAN OUTSIDE SAID SO.
I'M EARLY.
YOU KNOW, I WAS SUPPOSED
TO PICK YOU UP FROM YOUR
KARATE CLASS, RIGHT?
BUT YOUR FRIEND
PICKED ME UP INSTEAD.
SHE SAID HER NAME
WAS ALISON.
COME ON, WE SHOULD GO.
YOUR DAD'S PROBABLY
WONDERING WHERE WE ARE.
( phone ringing )
EMILY?
UM, MOM, I FIGURED
YOU'D BE HOME BY NOW.
I THOUGHT I WAS
CLEAR THIS MORNING.
LOOK, I KNOW YOU WANT ANSWERS,
BUT YOU CAN'T BE DOING THIS.
GO HOME.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT
THIS LATER.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
THIS IS NOT THE TIME.
WHY ARE THEY MAKING
YOU STAY LATE?
EMILY, GO.
I'LL CALL YOU
WHEN I'M ON MY WAY.
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR...
( humming coming
from the distance )
( humming continues )
( humming getting louder )
DIDN'T YOUR MOTHER HAVE THIS?
YOUR MOTHER.
REALLY, I MUST HAVE
LEFT IT AT YOUR HOUSE
AND DIDN'T GET IT BACK.
I LEFT A LOT
OF STUFF THERE.
IS IT JUST ME, OR WAS
SIXTH GRADE THE BEST YEAR EVER?
I DIDN'T EVEN
KNOW YOU THEN.
OH, HONEY,
YOU DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
ME WHEN YOU KNEW ME.
( music starts playing )
COME ON, GIVE IT UP,
SPENCE.
LET'S PRETEND THAT YOU'RE
GETTING READY FOR
YOUR FIRST BOY-GIRL
DANCE PARTY.
NO ONE EVER TELLS
YOU THAT THE PRACTICE
IS SO MUCH MORE FUN
THAN THE REAL THING.
Spencer:
WAS IT TOBY?
WAS HE THE ONE THAT
GAVE YOU THAT BLOODY LIP?
TOBY?
OH, SWEETIE,
GIRLS FIGHT MUCH
DIRTIER THAN BOYS.
I'M LUCKY SHE
DIDN'T LEAVE A SCAR.
SHE? WHO?
YOU STOPPED DANCING.
I DON'T--
I DON'T WANT TO DANCE.
I'LL CHANGE THE SONG.
NO, I CAN'T.
I HAVEN'T SLEPT
IN THREE DAYS.
COME ON.
I'M LOOKING
FOR SOMETHING.
THE STAR ON
MONA'S GAME BOARD.
OH, THAT.
IT'S IN THERE.
♪
Wren:
SPENCER.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
♪
SO...
YOU'RE MALCOLM'S
NEW HERO.
HE HAD A BLAST TONIGHT.
WHAT DID HE SAY?
AH, NOT MUCH.
MAGGIE SAID HE
MUMBLED SOMETHING
ABOUT PUPPETS,
AND THEN FELL
RIGHT TO SLEEP.
HUH.
OH, SHE ASKED ME TO
PASS ALONG HER THANKS.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU KEEP
SPOILING HIM LIKE THIS,
HE'S NOT GOING TO WANT
TO GO WITH ANYONE ELSE.
EZRA?
I DON'T THINK THAT
I CAN DO THIS ANYMORE.
ARIA, I WAS KIDDING.
YOU WON'T HAVE TO.
NO, I'M SAYING I DON'T THINK
THAT I CAN DO THIS ANYMORE.
WHAT?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
IT ISN'T JUST
THE TWO OF US NOW,
AND EVENTUALLY SOMEBODY'S
GOING TO WIND UP HURT.
AND I'D RATHER IT BE ME.
I JUST NEED TO GO HOME.
NOW? OKAY, WELL THEN,
JUST LET ME A WAITRESS--
NO.
YOU FINISH, I'M...
I'M GOING TO WALK.
I THINK THAT THE AIR
WILL BE GOOD FOR ME.
HEY.
I'VE HAD THESE DAYS.
I PROMISE YOU THINGS WILL
LOOK DIFFERENT IN THE MORNING.
Spencer:
HOW MANY TIMES
DID SHE VISIT HER?
WHAT IS THAT?
MONA KEPT SOUVENIRS.
HOW MANY TIMES
DID CECE VISIT HER?
I WOULDN'T KNOW.
YES, YOU WOULD, WREN.
YOU AUTHORIZED IT.
AND I WAS ALMOST
SUSPENDED FOR IT.
MONA WAS UNDER RESTRICTION
AT THAT TIME, NO VISITORS.
AND YOU BROKE THE RULES
FOR HER BECAUSE...?
CECE CALLED ME AND WAS
DESPERATE TO SEE HER.
SHE THOUGHT
SHE COULD HELP HER.
HELP HER WITH WHAT?
RECOVER FROM
THE PSYCHIC WOUNDS
INFLICTED BY YOUR
LATE FRIEND, ALISON.
YOU SURE IT WASN'T
THE OTHER WAY AROUND?
QUITE SURE. ALISON PULLED
SOME STUNT AT A FRAT PARTY
THAT GOT CECE KICKED OUT
OF UNIVERSITY.
ALLIE... GOT CECE
KICKED OUT OF SCHOOL?
YEAH, CECE CAME OUT
THE OTHER SIDE,
AND SHE THOUGHT SHE COULD
SERVE AS A ROLE MODEL FOR MONA.
AND I AGREED.
HOW DID SHE EVEN KNOW
THAT MONA WAS EVEN IN HERE?
MELISSA CALLED HER.
( knock on door )
EMILY?
IS HANNAH HOME?
NO. SHE'S OUT
WITH CALEB, WHY?
MOM?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHY WERE YOU CARRYING
THAT MISSING PERSONS FILE?
I PROMISED I WOULDN'T
KEEP ANYTHING FROM YOU.
BUT I HAVE TO MAKE SURE
THAT YOU KEEP THIS
FROM YOUR FRIENDS.
CAN I HAVE YOUR PHONE,
PLEASE?
WHAT?
THIS IS VERY SENSITIVE
INFORMATION,
IF IT GOT OUT BEFORE
THE POLICE--
MOM.
PLEASE, WHAT IS IT?
THEY FOUND ANOTHER BODY
EARLY THIS EVENING.
A YOUNG MAN.
LATE TEENS, EARLY 20S.
NO IDENTIFICATION.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
IT COULD BE TOBY?
I DON'T KNOW.
HOW CAN THEY NOT KNOW?
THERE WAS SIGNIFICANT TRAUMA
TO THE BODY, EMILY.
IT'S GONNA TAKE SOME TIME
BEFORE THEY'RE CERTAIN.
WE'LL KNOW MORE
TOMORROW MORNING.
♪
DO YOU WANT TO TAKE
A WALK OR SOMETHING?
IT WAS STUPID.
YOU GAVE SOMEONE
A SECOND CHANCE.
THAT'S NEVER STUPID.
WE TALKED ABOUT
THIS ROAD TRIP
WE WERE GONNA TAKE.
RIDE BIKES,
GO OUT WEST.
( sighing )
I WAS ALREADY
MAPPING IT OUT.
WE CAN TAKE
A TRIP SOMETIME.
I KNOW IT'S NOT
THE SAME, BUT--
IT WOULD BE BETTER.
BECAUSE I'LL BE WITH SOMEONE WHO
I KNOW IS LOOKING OUT FOR ME.
I'LL GET US REFILLS.
( bell tolling )
( phone ringing )
( bell continues tolling )
SO, BASICALLY A WAS FRAMING
JAMIE THE WHOLE TIME?
DO YOU THINK THAT BILL FROM
THE COLLECTION BOX WAS--
DON'T YOU?
CALEB IS NEVER GOING
TO FORGIVE ME.
WHERE IS HE NOW?
HE WENT TO GO FIND JAMIE.
BUT EVEN IF HE DOES,
WHAT IS HE SUPPOSED
TO TELL HIM?
HE MAY JUST HAVE TO FIND
A WAY TO TELL HIM THE TRUTH.
CALEB'S FAMILIAR WITH
THE WORKINGS OF A.
SO IS EZRA.
DO YOU PLAN ON
TELLING HIM WHO
BOUGHT HIS KID
A BIG,
FAT BALLOON TODAY?
( knock on door )
Aria: EM?
IT WAS THE WRONG BODY.
Hannah:
WHAT?
THE JOHN DOE,
THE ONE IN THE MASK.
IT WAS THE WRONG ONE.
EMILY,
YOU'RE NOT MAKING SENSE.
THEY JUST FOUND
A BODY TONIGHT.
IN A SHALLOW GRAVE
OUT IN THE WOODS.
WHERE?
EXACTLY WHERE
SPENCER SAID IT WAS.
THEY FOUND
HER PURSE CLOSE BY.
Mona's Voice: LOOK AT ALL
THAT'S HAPPENED SINCE
YOU TURNED ME DOWN ON OUR
LITTLE DRIVE UP THE MOUNTAIN.
BUT I BELIEVE
IN SECOND CHANCES.
Spencer's Voice: YOU DON'T HAVE
TO ASK ME AGAIN, MONA.
I'M IN.